I love you, Jun!
Can I get your response now?
Right after I started high school,
I made a confession.
It was, without question,
a confession of love!
You're just telling me this now, Tomo?
But...
I love you too, best bud!
Y-Yeah...
This dude doesn't even see me as a girl!
But I, Aizawa Tomo...
am a girl!
I Want to Be Seen as a Girl!
"I Want to Be Seen as a Girl!"
I'm heading out.
Aizawa
Heya, Tomo.
Hey...
This guy, Kubota Junichiro,
lives next door to me,
so we've hung out together
a lot since we were little.
We went to different elementary schools,
but in middle school...
We can finally walk home together!
You know...
You're getting a little too
crazy with that skirt!
What kind of new start are you making?
Huh?!
That was when I first realized
that Jun thought of me as a guy!
We're gonna miss the bus.
Let's move!
What's up?
This little...
What did I do?
Hmph!
By the way, I do karate.
Morning!
Hey.
Uenomizu High School
That stupid Jun!
Is he gonna treat me like a guy forever?
You gotta say something
to him for me, Misuzu!
Listen, Tomo...
I'm saying this as someone who's been
a friend to both of you for years.
Frankly, you're getting what you deserve.
Huh?
You only ever play games that boys play.
In middle school, you even fought
with kids from other schools.
And while I'm at it...
Even in kindergarten, whenever I asked
you to play house or dolls,
you never once played with me.
S-Sorry...
At this point, you might as
well just become a boy.
What do you say?
Don't ask me that!
What the heck? You're gonna
treat me like a guy, too?
Honestly, I'd like to, but...
Unlike Junichiro, I've seen certain things...
with a woman's eyes.
Anyway, your first problem
is the way you talk.
Yeah, but I can't just start
talkin' girly outta nowhere.
For starters, why not try
softening your tone a bit?
Try being more polite and less blunt.
Buying lunch from the school store?
What're you getting?
D-Do you mean me?
Gee, I don't know... Let me think...
Why are you talking like that?
You sound like an old man!
Old man...
Old man?!
What the hell is your problem?!
Huh?! What's your problem?!
Bring it!
Fine by me!
Whoa, wait! Time out!
Didn't you just tell me to bring it?!
I said knock it off!
I'm home.
Hey! Tomo!
What happened to your face?!
Ugh!
Got in a fight with Jun.
Jun-bo?!
You didn't lose to him, did you?!
Like I could win!
Don't be a wuss! You call yourself
the heir to the Aizawa style?!
Don't be crazy!
You've been teaching him karate too, Dad!
First of all, I'm a girl!
What'd you say?! Come to the dojo right now!
I'm gonna beat some guts into you!
Shut up, old man!
This is all because of the
stupid way you taught me!
All of it!
What are you talking about?!
C'mon, Tomo, I said I was
sorry about yesterday.
You're the one who hit me, anyway.
Just look at my face!
In fact, I feel like you've
been hitting me a lot lately.
Hey, c'mon! Talk to me already!
That is exactly why!
To be honest, I still don't really get it...
But I apologize, so don't be mad, okay?
Life's boring when you're not around.
I can't stand having you ignore
me for another second.
He's always like this
the day after we fight.
What is he trying to do to me?
F-Fine. I won't ignore you.
Really?!
You really are the best friend
I could ask for, Tomo!
Yeah, thanks.
He seriously doesn't get it!
You know, Tomo...
You and Junichiro always
come to school together,
and you're together throughout
the school day too, aren't you?
I guess so.
So why am I the one you
spend your lunch break with?
Well, I mean...
When a girl and a guy eat lunch
together, doesn't it look like...
they're dating or something?
Do you hear yourself?
But you'd rather eat lunch with him, right?
Huh?
Misuzu?
Leave it to me.
W-Wait, wait! What are you gonna do?!
The three of us can just eat together.
Not that! Anything but that!
You don't mind, do you, Junichiro?
What are you after, Gundo?
Why do I have to eat with you?
This isn't what I want, either.
This is why I didn't want to do this!
These two hate each other's guts!
Hey, that fried chicken looks good.
Here, you can have a piece.
Mm, that's good!
What do I do with these chopsticks now?!
Yo, Kubojun.
Hey, Tanabe.
Be honest. How far have you
gotten with Aizawa-san?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb!
What else could I mean but that intense
sport guys and girls do together?!
Intense sport guys and girls do together?
We've been doing that since we were kids.
Huh?!
For real?!
She does look like she has
a p-pretty amazing body!
Tomo's got good feet.
Good at using them, too.
Her feet?!
That's hardcore, man!
Junichiro was telling some guy that you and
he do an intense co-ed sport together.
Intense co-ed sport?
Oh, yeah, we do.
Not that sport.
Jun, you asshole!
Huh? Where'd that come from?
Whoa... Wait a...
Tanabe-kun, do you have a moment?
Gundo-san? Sure! No problem!
Huh? I misunderstood?
Yes. Those two aren't dating.
Junichiro doesn't even see Tomo as a girl.
Huh?!
Even though she's so... awesome?
I agree with you, but you're pure scum.
Anyway, I get it now. I didn't know
their relationship was so interesting.
Interesting?
There's no way both of
them feel nothing at all.
How can I give them a push?
Don't.
Oh, sorry.
You don't want anyone butting in
on your friends' love story, huh?
You've only known Junichiro since
starting high school, right?
Huh? Yeah...
Then remember this.
I'm the only one who's allowed
to play with those two.
P-Play?!
Oh, you forgot your umbrella, too?
Gundo...
I have one coming for me.
I have one coming for me, too.
Hey!
Does that mean it's a contest?
It does indeed.
Why are you beside me,
anyway? Go over there!
You really hate me, don't you?
The three of us used to play
together all the time, though.
Why did things turn out like this?
Yeah, the three of us did get up
to a lot of mischief together.
All the pranks you came
up with were so extreme.
But I never understood why...
Whenever the grown-ups yelled at us,
you were never around.
Wasn't I?
Why didn't you join any clubs?
You like sports, don't you?
I do karate at Tomo's family's dojo.
Besides, there's no point if boys' clubs
and girls' clubs are separate.
If I'm not in it with Tomo,
it wouldn't be any fun.
Seriously, what is your deal?
What deal?
If Tomo were to get a boyfriend...
Huh?
What would happen to you?
Have you ever imagined it?
Tomo cozying up to some guy who
isn't you, unbeknownst to you...
Then, with a red face, she says,
"There's no one else in
this world that I lo—"
Huh? What're you guys doing?
We both forgot our umbrellas.
Huh?
Just leave her and walk home with me.
Huh?!
Let's walk home together!
Why did you come to me?
I can't share an umbrella with him!
That's what I'm telling you to do.
Huh?! But...
Don't ask questions. Just go.
C'mon, get closer to me.
I-I'm fine right here.
No, you're not. You're getting wet.
I just came from practice,
so I smell sweaty.
That's what you're worried about?
You don't smell bad at all.
You idiot! Don't sniff me!
In fact, you smell kinda nice...
Hey! Tomo?!
Hey, Misuzu-chan!
"Misuzu-chan"?
Did you forget your umbrella?
Wanna get under mine?
You're sure?
Yeah, totally!
Just me alone, though?
Of course!
Thanks. You're pretty nice.
What the heck were you thinking?
Now you're soaking...
wet...
Huh? What... Jun?!
Wh-What the heck?
I seriously don't get him.
A Terrifying Challenge
"A Terrifying Challenge."
Aizawa-san is so amazing.
She's sharp, light on her feet, and...
stronger than anyone else!
My goddess has descended
into the karate club!
I'm sorry, Misaki-senpai!
I got all heated without realizing it...
You're still as strong as ever, huh?
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry about it.
Anyway, are you used to the boys' club now?
It must be tough being the only girl here.
Nah, I'm fine!
All the other students at my family's
dojo are guys, too, so I'm used to it.
If I'm being honest, I wish I could've had
this much fun with other girls, but...
Yeah, I bet. If you want to go back,
I can talk to someone for you.
I can't go back.
In the first match I got into to
test the new students' skills...
I got... a little carried away.
And after that, nobody
would practice with me.
I can see it. Even in the boys' club,
she's untouchable.
Boys' Karate Club
Girls' Karate Club
I joined the girls' club for
a change of surroundings...
And before I knew it, I was
surrounded by guys again.
Maybe I'm just a failure as a girl...
Th-That's not true!
I think... you're a very charming girl.
At least, that's how I see you.
Huh?!
It's the first time a guy ever
said something like that to me!
Please tell me, Senpai!
What about me seems girly?!
What should I put more emphasis on?!
Senpai, you've found my
womanly charm, right?!
Huh?!
S-S-Sorry! I wasn't looking!
I didn't find anything!
Nothing?!
I knew it...
N-Not that! That's not what I meant!
You have all kinds of charms!
But I don't think you should try
to emphasize just one thing.
I wouldn't want you to change like that.
You're plenty charming
just the way you are,
so I think you can have more
confidence in who you are now.
Today's the day we talk to Misaki-senpai!
Like, here he comes!
Hey, Senpai!
Thanks for your help today.
Like, who the heck is that?
He's pretty hot, too, though.
Wait, no! "He's" totally not!
She's wearing, like, a skirt,
and her boobs are, like, huge!
Like hell we're gonna let this happen!
What?
I hear Tomo has a friend
in the karate club.
Isn't that normal?
What are you smirking about?
A guy friend.
What's wrong? That's quite
the face you're making.
Oh, crap. I forgot my English textbook.
Jun, let me look at yours.
Sure.
Hey, Tomo...
I hear you made a friend
in the karate club.
You mean Misaki-senpai?
Misaki? And who is that?
The captain of the club.
Here's a pic.
Oh, it's a girl.
Are there any girls you're
closer to than Gundo?
Nope. Why?
I figured. I hate the thought of it, but...
How would you feel if she got a boyfriend?
If she got so wrapped up in him
that she stopped talking to you?
I can't even imagine
Misuzu being like that.
But... I guess...
I couldn't complain about it,
but I'd be a little lonely.
Right?!
Exactly! That's exactly it!
What are you talking about?
You're Aizawa-san from Class A, right?
I'm Mifune from Class B.
And, like, I'm Ogawa, also from Class B.
We wanna talk to you about
something. Meet us after school.
Like, behind the gym!
Doesn't sound like you're hoping
to become friends with me.
I dunno what you're up to,
but I don't get into half-assed fights.
Are you really ready for me?
Huh?
Figh...
I asked you if you're ready for me!
What the heck's her deal?!
She's, like, scary as hell!
You want to know about Aizawa-san?
Aizawa-san s-scares me!
I was matched up with her
in the karate club,
and her strength is seriously not human!
She moved to the boys' club
and still hasn't lost a match!
You're talking about a
fight with Aizawa-san?
I-I'd die if I fought with her!
Die? Am I... gonna die?
We gotta go apologize, like, right now!
These two girls I don't know picked
a fight with me outta nowhere.
I've never had an actual
throw-down with a girl before.
A throw-down?
You're not planning to
fistfight girls, are you?
C'mon, I'm not that ruthless!
I'll go easy on 'em.
High school girls don't
communicate with their fists.
I know that! But I'm not gonna make
nice with girls who pick fights!
I'm gonna take the initiative
and settle the score right—
You don't get it.
I think they just want to
verbally quarrel with you.
Verbally?
Yes. So you can't just come out swinging.
If you want to make counterarguments
or corrections, use your words.
Got it?
B-But...
No buts.
You really are frightening, you know that?
That said...
If they say anything too out of line, tell me.
I'll crush them socially.
I'd say you're a lot more
frightening than me.
Well? What is it you wanna say to me?
I-It's not that big a deal, really...
So for now...
Could you drop the fighting stance, at least?
Depends on what you say.
Carefully... Choose your words,
like, carefully!
I wanna go home right now!
S-See, there's... well... this guy we like...
And what's that got to do with me?
Well...
The guy we like is Misaki-senpai!
And we saw you being all
chummy with him, so...
So that's what this was about?
Huh?
You're saying...
You came to me for love advice
'cause I know Senpai?!
You should've said so from the start!
Huh?! Like, how did this happen?!
And why does she sound so happy?!
I never thought my little dream of giving
someone love advice would come true!
A girl who can be relied on in matters
of love is truly a girl among girls!
You want to get closer to Senpai, right?
So the first thing you gotta
do is be my friends!
If you're willing to accept
my help, I'm here.
S-Sure...
Why do I feel so reassured?
She's, like, so reliable somehow...
Man! I never thought I'd end
up giving love advice!
Feels like I'm totally
one of the girls now!
Maybe I actually have a
ton of feminine appeal?
I don't know about that.
Hey, Tomo.
Do you know what people called you
behind your back in middle school?
Huh? No idea.
The Natural Lady-Killer.
What the heck? I've never killed anyone.
Tomo! Let's hit up the school store!
Wait... Hang on, Jun!
All right! What do you wanna eat?
I don't...
She actually is a girl.
Totally a girl.
Seriously, he's so...
Just start treating me like a girl already!